<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CPhyGS: Cell Biology and Physiology Graduate Society</title>
    <description>CPhyGS is the Cell Biology and Physiology Graduate Society! Representing graduate students in both the Cellular and Physiological Sciences department, and in the Cell and Developmental Biology graduate program, here at the  beautiful University of British Columbia Come join us today!
</description>
    <link>http://cphygs.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://cphygs.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 23:47:43 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 23:47:43 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing CPhyGS</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Greetings everyone, we’re your new graduate student society representing
the CELL grad program and CPS department grad students!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our aim is to:&lt;br /&gt;
1. Provide professional development opportunities.&lt;br /&gt;
2. Create a strong sense of community.&lt;br /&gt;
3. Advocate on behalf of grad students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a lot of events in the works, and we’ll keep you updated as they develop.
But we’d love for you to help us! Send as an email at cphygs@gmail.com if you’d
like to join the planning committee (we’re real friendly!), or if you have any
suggestions or anything you’d like to discuss!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Sciencing!
- Your CPhyGS Planning Committee&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2030 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://cphygs.github.io/CphygsIntro.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cphygs.github.io/CphygsIntro.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Running Buffers Sun Run Team!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Love to run? Want to love to run? Want to pretend to love to run?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come on out and join the CPhyGS Running Buffers Sun Run team as we train
for the iconic 32nd annual Vancouver Sun Run! Featuring a 10k course
along the beautiful Vancouver seawall, the Sun Run is a perfect opportunity
to sweat and exercise your body after many long hours of hunchbacked pipetting.
And we can get brunch afterwards!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the extra ambitious, training runs are ongoing on Tuesday and Thursday mornings.
Contact Leslie Chan for details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/runningbufferslogo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Buffers Logo&quot; style=&quot;width: 200px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://cphygs.github.io/sports/runningbuffer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cphygs.github.io/sports/runningbuffer.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
