<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CPhyGS: Cell Biology and Physiology Graduate Society cphygs.github.io</title>
    <description>CPhyGS is the Cell Biology and Physiology Graduate Society! Representing graduate students in both the Cellular and Physiological Sciences department, and in the Cell and Developmental Biology graduate program, here at the  beautiful University of British Columbia Come join us today!
</description>
    <link>http://cphygs.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://cphygs.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 13:48:17 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 13:48:17 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing CPhyGS</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Greetings everyone, we’re your new graduate student society representing
the CELL grad program and CPS department grad students!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our aim is to:&lt;br /&gt;
1. Provide professional development opportunities.&lt;br /&gt;
2. Create a strong sense of community.&lt;br /&gt;
3. Advocate on behalf of grad students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a lot of events in the works, and we’ll keep you updated as they develop.
But we’d love for you to help us! Send as an email at cphygs@gmail.com if you’d
like to join the planning committee (we’re real friendly!), or if you have any
suggestions or anything you’d like to discuss!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Sciencing!
- Your CPhyGS Planning Committee&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2030 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://cphygs.github.io/CphygsIntro.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cphygs.github.io/CphygsIntro.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Running Buffers Sun Run Team!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Love to run? Want to love to run? Want to pretend to love to run? 
Come on out and join the CPhyGS Running Buffers Sun Run team as we train for the iconic 32nd annual Vancouver Sun Run! Featuring a 10k course
along the beautiful Vancouver seawall, the Sun Run is a perfect opportunity
to sweat and exercise your body after many long hours of hunchbacked pipetting.
And we can get brunch afterwards! &lt;strong&gt;March 17&lt;/strong&gt; is the team signup deadline!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the extra ambitious, training runs are ongoing on Tuesday and Thursday mornings.
Contact Leslie Chan for details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/runningbufferslogo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Running Buffers Logo&quot; style=&quot;width: 200px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://cphygs.github.io/runningbuffer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cphygs.github.io/runningbuffer.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trivia Night! Mar TBD</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey CELL program and CPS department,
We are planning a Trivia Night for you guys to test your knowledge and have 
some well deserved fun. This event will occur in March, but the details have yet to 
be decided upon. If you have concerns, comments, or suggestions on how you would like the Trivia 
Night event to go down, please attend our bi-annual Open Meeting scheduled 
February 10th, 2016 in LSI 1330 at 1pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your CPhyGS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://cphygs.github.io/TriviaNight.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cphygs.github.io/TriviaNight.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alumni and Careers Night: Apr TBD</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know there are careers outside of academia? Do you love Vancouver? Who doesn’t! Well this night could be the night for you!  We have invited established UBC alumni working in relevant fields in Vancouver to share their experiences with you, in an informal setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are planning to have this event mid-April in the evening (so that beer can be served!). Please stay tuned and let us know if you have an illustrious alumni that you think would like to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://cphygs.github.io/AlumniNight.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cphygs.github.io/AlumniNight.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
